

# **SUMMARY**

Hello! My name is Giorgio and I'm a software developer with a passion for UX design. I like to implement creative solutions for modern User Interfaces.

# **ADDITIONAL INFO**

Through my work experiences I used different types of programming languages, most of them are the following:

- Javascript & Typescript
- Java
- Python
- HTML
- CSS (SCSS & Styled Components)
- C#

#### CONTACTS

E-mail: capaccio.giorgio@gmail.com Telephone: +39 3880762087 Address: Via Eugenio Curiel 7 40134 Bologna

# GIORGIO CAPACCIO

# SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

#### **CAREER SUMMARY**

#### **IBM - Consultant in SOGEL**

# Experience Front End Developer | Aug 2023 - Ongoing

• FE Development for Ministry of Economy and Finance

# Accenture s.p.a. - Experience Consultant in Enel

# Software Developer | feb 2023 - Aug 2023

• Back end development in Java and SQL

#### Accenture s.p.a. - Accenture (AIP+ Rapid)

#### Software Developer (R&D) | sep 2021 - jan 2023

- Development and implementation of Design Language components with React
- Development of little back end services in Java and Python

#### **ALTEN - Consultant in Alstom**

# Software Developer in Alstom | gen 2021 - sep 2021

• Development and testing functionalities and solutions for a Traffic Management System in C#, .NET framework

# **Retail Italia srl**

#### Web Developer | oct 2019 - dec 2020

 Development and testing of Single Page Applications in Angular8

# **EDUCATION**

# **Alma Mater Studiorum - Computer Engineering**

Student | Oct 2022 - Ongoing

Bachelor student of computer engineering

#### Google UX Design (Professional Certificates)

Coursera Courses | March 2021

- 1. Foundations of User Experience Design
- 2.UX Design Process

## **GiGroup Angular Academy**

Course | Aug 2019 - Oct 2019

Intensive course of Angular fundamentals

# ITIS Leonardo Da Vinci - Lanciano

High School Diploma | July 2011

High School Diploma in Electronics and TLC